
var title = "The Alphabet: enter each letter's name";

var questions = [

  {
    prompt: "Α, α",
    answer: ["άλφα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Β, β",
    answer: ["βήτα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Γ, γ",
    answer: ["γάμμα", "γάμα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Δ, δ",
    answer: ["δέλτα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ε, ε",
    answer: ["έψιλον"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ζ, ζ",
    answer: ["ζήτα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Η, η",
    answer: ["ήτα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Θ, θ",
    answer: ["θήτα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ι, ι",
    answer: ["γιώτα", "ιώτα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Κ, κ",
    answer: ["κάππα", "κάπα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Λ, λ",
    answer: ["λάμδα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Μ, μ",
    answer: ["μι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ν, ν",
    answer: ["νι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ξ, ξ",
    answer: ["ξι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ο, ο",
    answer: ["όμικρον"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Π, π",
    answer: ["πι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ρ, ρ",
    answer: ["ρο"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Σ, σ/ς",
    answer: ["σίγμα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Τ, τ",
    answer: ["ταυ"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Υ, υ",
    answer: ["ύψιλον"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Φ, φ",
    answer: ["φι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Χ, χ",
    answer: ["χι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ψ, ψ",
    answer: ["ψι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "Ω, ω",
    answer: ["ωμέγα"],
    partial: [],
  },
];
